Seino
Here we are, everyone!
Ta-da!
Can you read?
We've arrived at Miyazaki Bougainvillea Airport!
Oh! We're here!
Miyazaki Prefecture.
What's the middle of the airport? We're...
We're in the middle of 46 Hours of Hyugaizaka TV.
That's right.
It's the morning of the second day, right?
It's the morning of the 22nd.
You just arrived, right?
Yes, sir.
Descent.
We're a live broadcast team.
We're here in Miyazaki.
After this, we'll be broadcasting live on 46 Hours TV.
We are going to Miyazaki Central Wholesale Market.
We're going to Miyazaki Central Wholesale Market.
Yes! Look forward to seeing what's in store for you!
What are you going to do?
Yes, I'm flying. Ready, go!
Good morning everyone, I'm Matsuda Onoka.
I'm Haruka Yamashita.
Good morning.
Crunchy.
Delicious!
Thank you very much.
It's like I came to get you.
Well, just a little while ago... the 46 Hours TV show was on live TV.
Good morning.
It's over, but it's over... how was it?
Well, it was difficult. It was my first time.
Eating, talking, listening... I'm not used to it.
I'd like to sign your autograph.
Thank you so much.
A red pen? You know a red pen?
That's great!
I see it all the time.
Thank you so much.
We're out of pens.
Did you get the order yet?
I told Mr. Satomi.
I'm so glad.
You know me so well.
May I use your site?
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
It's your first time at St. Marin.
Of course.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
First time at the marin, right?
That's right.
I'm really looking forward to working with you.
We'd really appreciate it if you could help us.
Thank you very much.
We'll see you next time.
This one, too.
Amazing towels!
Yamatozaka's.
It's true.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad
Amazing.
We've found the sun.
Charge!
Oh!
It's Shiho and Meimei!
Please don't go that far!
Ehhhh...
Tears
I cried tears!
Please come!
Please come to the Hyuga Festival!
Oh, two days?
Both days.
Thank you very much.
Will you come to the Hyuga Festival, too?
I know it's a long way, but I can feel your love.
It's about 500 meters away.
Thank you very much.
Have a safe trip home.
I'll wait for you.
Thank you very much.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Is he on the phone?
I'm sorry.
Would you please reproduce the letter?
Of course.
Yes, of course.
That's great.
You noticed.
And here.
It's true.
Thank you.
So many posters.
So many!
Thank you very much.
a crime against humanity
something
Hello.
Miyazaki's gyoza ranked No. 1 in Japan
What! That's amazing!
No. 1 in the whole country?
It's true!
It's not too much to say that Miyazaki is the best when it comes to gyoza!
Wow!
Mr. Yatai Bone!
Excuse me.
Wow!
Another poster here.
We support you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me.
You've already prepared it.
This looks delicious!
It's made with Miyazaki brand coke.
It's filled with fresh vegetables and pork.
Amazing!
It's filled with Miyazaki!
Gyoza filled with Miyazaki.
Amazing.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bon appétit!
Cute size.
It's true, it's small. It's like an ear.
Bon appétit.
Sounds good.
I don't want to talk. I don't want to talk. I want to spread it in my mouth.
I want to spread it in my mouth. I want to taste it. It's so delicious.
It smells so good, just being next to it.
I can smell it? It smells so good, it's so good, you know that sound you heard earlier?
Crunching. It goes on and on forever.
It's delicious.
It's delicious. It looks good. It looks good.
Bon appétit!
It's really crispy. I can hear it.
I know it's going to be really crispy when I see it.
But this is more than I expected.
This brown browned part is especially crispy.
Oh, it's delicious.
Really crispy.
It made my throat water.
It's true. This is the place.
So you want to eat before the show.
It's good.
I'm sure it's not just the members who have to shout, but the fans as well, so after recharging your stamina with gyoza...
We'd love to have you join us after recharging your energy with gyoza.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for letting us go around the market.
I've been all over town.
Well, the whole town is a lot of fun.
Yes, but... the market... the whole market... is so exciting.
Thank you very much.
It was so nice. It was so warm.
I thought, "We have to make this a big success at the Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium.
Yes, I thought even more.
After this.
That's right.
We will be broadcasting live on MRT.
Wow, what am I going to do?
I'm so nervous.
I'd like to move over there.
Okay, I'm off!
Let's go!
We're here at MRT Miyazaki Broadcasting.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a while since I've been here.
I'll be back later with the live broadcaster, myself, and our soba noodles.
Oh! Soba making in Miyazaki?
Then let's spread your soba in Miyazaki.
I'll do my best to spread the word.
I'll do my best.
I'm off!
I'm off! Okay, so we're not in the MRT Miyazaki Broadcasting studio, are we?
This is a conference room where they've set up a special soba set.
But... And your outfit?
Yes, I've changed my clothes, and the live broadcast is coming.
I'll have to finish the soba there.
I have to finish my soba there, but in the spring...
I will be appearing in other programs and on the radio, so I will be supporting you.
Thank you very much.
Please do your best.
Let's do our best. I'll be rooting for you.
Good luck again.
Thank you very much. I'm off. Good luck.
Okay, I'll shake it up then.
Okay.
I didn't think we'd be doing this three times during the 46 hours of TV.
You're like an idol or a soba craftsman.
You're already early.
I'll soon be appearing on a show called Mr. Following's Saturday!
I'll be talking about the Hyuga Festival and why I'm here in Miyazaki.
I'll be making announcements about the Hyuga Festival and talking about why I'm here in Miyazaki.
I'll do my best while having fun!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll have one!
Thank you very much!
Hello everyone!
This is Haruka Yamashita from Hotty6.
I'm here in Miyazaki prefecture for the 7 live broadcast of Hyuga Valley 46 Hour TV.
How did you like it?
It was really nice.
So kind!
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, the live broadcast was over, and right after that, all of my co-stars were so kind and helpful,
They even gave me the nickname "Haruharu," which is my nickname.
The set is already here. I don't want to leave.
I will do my best so that we can perform together again. Thank you very much.
Haruharu, are you doing well? I wonder if you are on the radio right now.
I'd love to listen to the radio.
Shall I invite you to the studio? Please come in.
I'm Haruka Yamashita from Minatozuka 46. Pleased to meet you.
Welcome. It's been a wonderful summer.
What's that sound?
What's happening?
What's going on?
Minatozuka46.
I'd like to ask you something...
Everyone in Miyazaki Prefecture...
Why don't you spend some time talking with Hyugaizaka 46
Why don't you come and spend some time talking with Hyuga-saka 46 at Sun Marine Stadium Miyazaki?
We are looking forward to seeing you!
We're waiting for you!
I love Miyazaki!
I just had a chance to appear on the radio a few minutes ago.
I'm so sorry, everyone in Miyazaki prefecture.
I'm so sorry... for listening to you.
I'm so sorry for the chaos.
But I'd like to make an announcement.
I hope I was able to convey that I love Miyazaki Prefecture.
I hope I was able to convey the message that I love Miyazaki Prefecture.
I'm going to a certain place.
And by "certain place," I mean this umbrella place.
Let's meet the master.
Master is making soba noodles.
He's on his way there.
Yes, sir.
Master.
Hey.
I'm home.
How was it?
I was nervous. I was thinking about you.
I've been talking.
Really?
Wow, that's great.
A little more.
Tottori seems to be winding up unexpectedly.
I'm Yamashita from Miyazaki.
I'm here to talk to MRT Miyazaki Broadcasting.
Tanaka-san is making soba noodles again.
Bon appétit!
I don't know about that.
Will Matsuda-san's handmade soba be at the Hyuga Festival?
Yes.
Oh!
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, we're live now.
Yes, the 46-hour TV broadcast is over.
It's over now.
I feel relieved
Yes, yes, yes.
You finished making it, didn't you?
I finished making it, didn't I?
My morning buckwheat noodles...
They told us we could exhibit at the festival.
I was so relieved.
It was really delicious.
I'm glad.
All the comments from the judges were so true.
I'm glad to hear that you agree.
I've seen you on TV and radio... but there was something wrong with you.
I could say the dialect... and he used the key word "Haruharu"...
Yes it's too warm and red and sober... thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
It really was UMatsuda!
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the festival!
I'm sorry you had to come all the way to MRT again.
Actually, there's one more thing I'd like you two to see.
What's that?
We're preparing something.
May I ask you to come downstairs?
Sure.
I have something I'd like to show you two.
I'm looking forward to it.
Can we just move along, please?
Yes, let's go.
Pleasure to meet you.
Yes, ma'am.
Now you're going to show me something, right?
We're on the first floor of MRT.
We're here on the first floor of the MRT, and we're in the same building as MRT MIC.
We're going to go in there.
Let's go!
What is it?
I see something!
They're shopping.
Right this way.
Oh, my God.
And only 77 days to go.
This paper.
That's right.
The people of Miyazaki wrote on them, didn't they?
This way, right?
When Mr. Yamashita visited us before.
When Mr. Yamashita came before, the Hyuga Saka booth was over there.
We've moved it to a new location because the Hyuga Festival is coming soon.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
A little closer to the entrance.
That's right.
It was rather easy to see.
It's kind of a prominent location.
Thank God for that.
That's great.
So, this is the finished booth.
This booth actually has a title.
We'd like to hold an unveiling ceremony.
Unveiling ceremony
Are you moving to the side?
Yes, the unveiling ceremony.
Please do it.
Ready...
There it is!
What's it say?
Wait.
Almost there.
It's still there.
A little more.
It's done.
That's great.
Can you see it?
This way.
Yes, sir.
This is the Sunshine Kone Plaza.
Kone Plaza.
Is this Miyazaki dialect?
That's exactly right.
It means "Come here.
Kone?
That's right.
Before and after the festival.
We opened this time.
Thank you so much.
Good night.
We really appreciate all the colorful papers you wrote and posters you sent us.
and posters that you sent to us.
It was a very fulfilling exhibition!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
You look so happy, so happy!
Thank you so much.
I hope you will all take the time to look back and enjoy the exhibition.
I hope you'll take the time to look at it.
The sun is not shining!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Lastly, since we're here...
Could you sign one of them?
Of course.
Thank you very much.
The sun was shining so brightly on us.
I'd like to take this opportunity to thank all of you who came out today to support the 46-hour TV event.
In fact, people who want to make the Hyuga Festival more exciting in Miyazaki Prefecture have gathered together.
The Hyugaizaka Study Group is a group of people who want to make the Hyuga Festival a great success.
I was wondering if you would be interested in going to this event?
I'd like to go.
It's a group of people who want to make the Hyuga Festival more exciting.
I'd love to go!
By the way...
The people who are attending the workshop don't know that you two are coming.
Oh!
You should go.
I'm so nervous.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Wakakusa Huppe, where the study group is being held...
It looks like it's already around here.
Where is it?
Look, look, look!
Sun study group!
Wow!
It's got writing on it.
Sun Study Group, second floor.
Look! Sunshine! Look! It's all white!
It's so white!
Box.
When is it ever this sunny?
Amazing, isn't it?
Let's go in.
We met on Saturday, June 22nd, right?
Oh, my God, second period, third period...
And, wait, they're popping up everywhere.
Historical books.
You mean the 2:00 to 4:00 p.m. one?
I slept through the whole morning.
Thank you.
I got your question.
I'm curious.
We are also maybe there are some people who don't know yet,
Hinakawadakawa46.
Yes, I understand.
I am nervous.
Surprise.
I'm HinakawaDakawa46.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
As HinakawaDakawa46, we are now doing a 46-hour TV show on youtube channel.
The purpose of this TV program is to promote the Hyuga Festival that will be held in Miyazaki in September.
I heard that a study session was being held in Miyazaki, so I thought it would be a good surprise if I could come and visit.
Oh, oh, oh!
It's so crowded!
I'm so surprised.
Amazing!
It's amazing, really amazing.
Thank you very much.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
That's a great towel.
Thank you very much.
I heard that the Hyuga Festival will be held.
I'm sorry to be honest.
I didn't know much about it.
That's right.
If you are going to have an event in September
The fans, the sun, and the members
and the sun and the members.
I'm doing this workshop with the concept
I'm holding this study session with the concept of warmly welcoming the fans, the sun and the members.
Thank you very much.
We started at 10:30 in the morning, and we had a second circle and stuff like that.
That's great.
Like that before the test.
I was just saying that's really great.
But one thing I was wondering about was the sun financier.
Yes, yes.
It says that if you join today, you'll get a sunset financier.
Thank you very much.
It's his honey financier, and this is his sky-blue financier.
Cheese buns!
What a fateful reunion!
Another financier.
Then I'll have some.
Okay, then, everyone.
Cheers to the success of the Hinata Fest!
Cheers!
Delicious!
Nice to meet you.
Bank with honey from Miyazaki.
Amazing.
With Japan's Hyuga Ocean.
Delicious!
Delicious.
I'd like to know your guesses and stuff.
The cheese buns I bought.
What?
Natto cheese buns.
Natto (fermented soybeans).
Seeing them like this, it motivates us even more.
We have to work hard too!
It really cheered me up.
Thank you very much!
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
You're very warm.
Let's do it.
It's true.
Let's hold hands.
So... this is Miyazaki Station.
I was just in the sun study group.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to repay the favor with lots of power.
I'll go put up posters.
Appointment?
Appointment.
Appointments make me nervous.
Hey, making an appointment...
Do you have any tips?
Tips?
It's not a feeling anymore, is it?
Mind!
Mind.
And luck.
Luck.
So you want to negotiate with this store to put up the posters?
Yes, let's do it.
Give me your camera.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Hello.
We're from an idol group called Hyugaizaka 46.
We'll be performing at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium on September 7th and 8th.
We will be performing at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium on September 7 and 8.
We would really appreciate it if you could buy posters and stuff for us.
Is that all right?
Of course.
Thank you very much.
By the way, is it OK if we take pictures?
Can we do it here?
It's a really nice place, isn't it?
Wow.
Wow, thank you very much.
Thank you for the best view.
I'll be there.
I'm nervous.
Hi. - Hi.
Excuse me.
Um...
We're an idol group called
We're an idol group.
Excuse me.
How was it?
What do you think?
You seem to be smiling, so I think you'll be fine.
It was fine.
Yay!
I was so nervous.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Look, look, look.
I put it in a very prominent place.
I've put it up.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.
It's so warm.
It's too homey.
You've been waving to us the whole time.
That's so nice.
It's so warm.
It's amazing.
We really are a family.
We're a family.
We're family.
Really family.
Really Family
They came in.
I was so nervous.
I'm Matsuda Konoka.
I can hear you so well.
This coming September.
I'm going to hold a festival at the Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium.
I'm going to hold a festival called Hyuga Fest at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium.
And we'd like to invite the people of Miyazaki
I'd love for everyone in Miyazaki to come.
You're a master, aren't you?
He was very smooth.
Thank you for watching.
It's so beautiful.
I got it!
It's a screen door, isn't it?
It's a screen door.
I'm so glad I put it up.
I got it!
Thank you so much for letting me put it up.
Thank you very much.
This is a great glass walled store.
It would be great if we could put up some posters.
It's a great spot, isn't it? It's a corner.
You can see it from all sides.
Looks good, doesn't it?
Are you busy?
I'll see what I can do.
Excuse me.
There's an idol group called Hyuhizaka 46.
I know them.
You know them? Thank you very much.
We'd like to put up a PR poster here in the store.
I'll go check it out.
Yes, please.
Oh, no, it's a mess.
It was fine.
I checked with the manager, and he said it's fine.
Thank you very much.
It's about unsellable.
Hello, Carbonaia's.
Japan Dersic Sauce
it's been a while.
Thank you.
I'm waiting for the eggs you promised.
Oh, I'm so happy!
That's great.
Bring them in, please.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
Shall we go to one more?
Yes, let's go.
Where would you like to go? Here?
The father of the festival?
It's called the Hinata festival.
It's connected to the festival.
That's true.
I feel a connection. I'll ask him.
I'll ask him.
Hello.
I'm glad you let us put up the posters.
I think it's safe to say that
I think it's not surprising that you've already conquered Amy Road.
I don't know.
How was it?
I was nervous.
Nervous?
Oh, good!
I'm nervous right now.
Thank you so much for doing this.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
So... we're going to need you to go around the area now and put up posters.
I've been putting up posters.
I've been putting up posters around the area, and I think they're getting lighter and lighter.
We will have another live broadcast later in the evening, but we had a limited time.
But everyone was very warm and welcoming, and we even got to see the sun.
I'm so happy for you.
I heard many people say that they knew about the festival the moment I told them about it, so I was really happy to hear that.
I hope more people will see the poster and decide to come.
Well, we're running out of time, so let's move on.
It's big!
Here we are!
Oh!
Mr. Susen!
Yes!
It's been a while.
When I was on location in Miyazaki.
I had dinner with Audrey and other staff members.
I was one of the people surrounding Mr. Wakabayashi.
I'm one of the people who surrounded Mr. Wakabayashi.
Shall we go there to negotiate for posters?
Yes, posters.
Okay.
Thank you.
What? Wait.
Here.
This is the time, right?
This is it.
You didn't write Haruharu's signature on it?
MIRE and KUMI came to the store at that time and gave us take-out.
Hello. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Thank you for always taking care of us. I am a member of Hinatazaka 46,
We have already put up the poster of Hyuga Pesu on our album.
Thank you very much.
We were wondering if we could put them up if you don't mind.
Yes, I would.
Oh, may I?
Really? Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
It's something I really wanted to do.
I'll put it up.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
That's a great lineup.
I'm so happy.
Yes, I am.
Thank you very much.
Yay.
That's how it's done.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Sashimi platter.
I'll have the grilled thigh.
Chicken number one, please.
That's all.
What? Are you sure? Here we go.
Soba... again.
How many times do we have to do it again?
But... at a festival...
If I say Yoshika Matsuda's handmade soba...
I'll have to do it all the time.
Right...
I've never been more than one volume ahead of time.
"One volume advance" is a trip.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the chicken nanban.
You're glowing.
It's shining. It's really shining.
You see?
It's good, right?
It wasn't chicken nanban, was it? When you brought it to me.
Chicken Nanban.
I'll have the chicken nanban.
One more take, please.
One more take? Was that bad?
Stylish take.
Fashionable take?
I'll have the chicken nanban, please.
Yay! What's this?
Oh my God...
He definitely wants to see it.
I'm a bad junior.
I'm sure there are people who'd like to see it.
Good. Good.
I'm going to eat.
Let's eat.
Here you go.
Moist and crispy coexist.
It's a great coexistence!
Chicken Nanban.
Oh, then it's not that interesting take.
I've had enough of this.
I'll leave you alone for the rest of the show.
It's a footbath.
I can do it.
Good night.
Chicken Lamburin' for you, sir.
Don't look at it.
No, it's for me.
You don't see many people looking at you when you eat.
Bon appétit!
You can hear the sound... a little crispy.
I'll pull out my teeth.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
I'm really happy to have local food from Miyazaki, and I hope that at the Hyuga Festival, people can enjoy not only the food from the festival, but also the local products.
And at the Hyuga Festival, if people can enjoy not only the food from the festival, but also the local products...
I'm sure the people of Miyazaki will be pleased as well.
Yes.
I hope we can all get together and enjoy the festival.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll be waiting for you.
That's right.
Mizuki dialect
Seino
Matcho yo
What do you think of our
Okay, I'm going back to the studio.
Well, that's it.
That concludes our live coverage of the second day of the 46-hour program.
Thank you very much.
Some of you may have been wondering about the sound...
This way.
Actually, it's like this.
We had a footbath in the hot spring.
It really warmed me up.
It was so warm!
Tomorrow, there will be another 46-hour TV program.
I would like to go back to Tokyo after the 46-hour TV program.
I'd like to go back to Tokyo.
But this time, you know...
We were the only two people who could come to Miyazaki for the 46-hour TV program.
We're the only two who could come to Miyazaki for the 46-hour TV program.
I want you to enjoy it as much as you can.
And to the members.
I hope to be able to tell the members about what happened.
I hope to be able to tell the members about it.
We put up a lot of posters for PR this time.
I'd be happy if people come to the festival because of that.
I would be very happy.
Thank you very much.
As this is the last time
I'm sad.
I hope to see you again.
I hope to see you all again in September.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all again in September.
I'll be waiting for you.
Subscribe to our channel and click the good button!
I'll see you at the Hyuga Festival!
Bye bye!